<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TugasPPAB07</string>
    <string name="tab_1_name">Film</string>
    <string name="tab_2_name">Book</string>


    <string-array name="filmTitle">
        <item>Ironman 1</item>
        <item>Ironman 2</item>
        <item>Ironman 3</item>
        <item>The Avengers</item>
        <item>Avengers: Age of Ultron</item>
        <item>Avengers: Infinity War</item>
        <item>Avengers: Endgame</item>
        <item>The Hobbit: An Unexpected Journey</item>
        <item>The Hobbit: The Desolation of Smaug</item>
        <item>The Hobbit: The Battle of the Five Armies</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="filmYear">
        <item>2008</item>
        <item>2010</item>
        <item>2013</item>
        <item>2012</item>
        <item>2015</item>
        <item>2018</item>
        <item>2019</item>
        <item>2012</item>
        <item>2013</item>
        <item>2014</item>
    </string-array>

    <integer-array name="filmCover">
        <item>@drawable/ironman_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/ironman_2</item>
        <item>@drawable/ironman_3</item>
        <item>@drawable/theavengers_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/theavengers_2</item>
        <item>@drawable/theavengers_3</item>
        <item>@drawable/theavengers_4</item>
        <item>@drawable/thehobbit_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/thehobbit_2</item>
        <item>@drawable/thehobbit_3</item>
    </integer-array>

    <string-array name="filmSynopsys">
        <item>Billionaire, genius, playboy, philanthropist? All this and more sums up Tony Stark. After a weapons presentation in Iraq, Stark gets himself captured which also results in him having a chest filled with shrapnel. Needing to escape, he miniaturizes it and dons a suit of armor. This results in the birth of the Armored Avenger Iron Man. Once returned safely, Stark works to perfect his design and uses it to protect all mankind. This activity catches the eye of a mysterious organization known as SHIELD. On the other hand, the chairman of Stark Industries discovers this and has plans of his own for Tonys work.</item>
        <item>Six months have passed since Tony Stark has defeated his former friend, Obidah Stane aka the Iron Monger and he has publicly revealed his identity to the world. Tony is facing many issues with his life, such as using palladium for his arc reactor which is causing serious problems towards his health and a rival inventor named Justin Hammer wants to put Stark Industries out of business so that he can become the top inventor. Tonys recklessness is reaching its breaking point for him when his friendship with Rhodey at risk and his love for Pepper in serious jeopardy. However, Tony is soon faced with another issue when Ivan Vanko aka Whiplash begins to seek revenge on him for getting his late father, Anton dismissed from Stark Industries by Howard many years ago. With the stakes held high for Tony, he must form new alliances with Natasha Romanoff and Nick Fury, who are both agents of S.H.I.E.L.D. in order to defeat Hammer and Vanko once and for all.</item>
        <item>In Malibu California, Tony Stark has insomnia and over 72 hours he develops the new prototype MK42 of the Iron Man armature. He also recalls events in 1999, in Bern, Switzerland, when he had one night stand with the genetic scientist Maya Hansen that was researching a regenerative process and made fun of his fan Aldrich Killian on the New Year eve. There are explosions in Los Angeles and the terrorist Mandarin assumes the attempts broadcasting through television. When Tony bodyguard and friend Happy Hogan is seriously wounded in an explosion, Tony Stark challenges Mandarin and gives his address to him. However, three helicopters attack his mansion and he loses everything but his prototype, and he awakes in the Tennessee. Tony tries to make work the defective prototype and soon he discovers that the event from 1999 is connected to the present terrorist attacks.</item>
        <item>S.H.I.E.L.D. has located the mysterious Tesseract device and the Army super soldier Captain America. The Tesseract is actually a gateway to an entirely new world called Asgard. A mysterious being known as Loki arrives on earth and immediately assumes that he can rule all human beings. But that irks S.H.I.E.L.D. director Nick Fury the wrong way. As Loki escapes with the Tesseract, Nick Fury believes this is an act of war against Earth. His only hope is to assemble an actual team of super heroes. Dr. Bruce Banner, who turns into an enormous green rage monster known as the Hulk. Tony Stark and his venerable Iron Man armor. Captain America, the Stark Enterprises created super soldier. Thor, the god of thunder, protector of Earth and his home planet of Asgard, and Loki brother. Master assassins Hawkeye and Natasha Romanoff. Together they will become a team to take on an attack that will call them to become the greatest of all time.</item>
        <item>After a successful raid on a HYDRA base, Tony Stark and Bruce Banner create an Artificial Intelligence called Ultron, a peacekeeping protocol designed to help the Avengers protect the world from their enemies. But things go wrong when Ultron sees the human race as a threat and sets out to destroy it along with the Avengers. Now the Avengers, Iron Man, Thor, Captain America, the Hulk, Black Widow and Hawkeye, must reassemble to stop Ultron from causing mass destruction. Aside from this, the Avengers also must take on the powerful twins Quicksilver and Scarlet Witch as well as the new entity called Vision. Also, the Avengers find that things may never be the same again after discovering a power beyond their comprehension.</item>
        <item>As the Avengers and their allies have continued to protect the world from threats too large for any one hero to handle, a new danger has emerged from the cosmic shadows: Thanos. A despot of intergalactic infamy, his goal is to collect all six Infinity Stones, artifacts of unimaginable power, and use them to inflict his twisted will on all of reality. Everything the Avengers have fought for has led up to this moment, the fate of Earth and existence has never been more uncertain.</item>
        <item>After half of all life is snapped away by Thanos, the Avengers are left scattered and divided. Now with a way to reverse the damage, the Avengers and their allies must assemble once more and learn to put differences aside in order to work together and set things right. Along the way, the Avengers realize that sacrifices must be made as they prepare for the ultimate final showdown with Thanos, which will result in the heroes fighting the biggest battle they have ever faced.</item>
        <item>Bilbo Baggins is swept into a quest to reclaim the lost Dwarf Kingdom of Erebor from the fearsome dragon Smaug. Approached out of the blue by the wizard Gandalf the Grey, Bilbo finds himself joining a company of thirteen dwarves led by the legendary warrior, Thorin Oakenshield. Their journey will take them into the Wild; through treacherous lands swarming with Goblins and Orcs, deadly Wargs and Giant Spiders, Shapeshifters and Sorcerers. Although their goal lies to the East and the wastelands of the Lonely Mountain first they must escape the goblin tunnels, where Bilbo meets the creature that will change his life forever Gollum. Here, alone with Gollum, on the shores of an underground lake, the unassuming Bilbo Baggins not only discovers depths of guile and courage that surprise even him, he also gains possession of Gollums precious ring that holds unexpected and useful qualities A simple, gold ring that is tied to the fate of all Middle-earth in ways Bilbo cannot begin to know.</item>
        <item>As Gandalf the Grey, Bilbo Baggins and Dwarf King Thorin II Oakenshield long and perilous journey to the heart of the Lonely Mountain continues, a relentless pursuit by the vicious orc, Azog, will inevitably lead the brave fellowship into the dark forests of Mirkwood. Without the sage wizard guidance, both hobbit and dwarves must keep on venturing into danger undeterred, concentrating solely on their primary mission to retrieve the stolen Arkenstone from Smaug. But atop a mountain of Erebor pilfered gold, the omnipotent drake is waiting silently, ready to put up a fight for his beloved treasure. Who dares to challenge him?</item>
        <item>Atop the reclaimed Lonely Mountain, Bilbo Baggins and the fellowship of Dwarves witness the mighty winged drake, Smaug, swooping down upon Laketown in a fit of fiery rage, as refugee denizens and Elves converge on Erebor to claim the realm inestimable treasure. However, as Prince Thorin II Oakenshield rapidly succumbs to the hypnotic allure of the corrupting mounds of gold, friendships shatter over greed, and a war is brewing in Middle-Earth that will decide the fate of all living souls.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="bookTitle">
        <item>Harry Potter and the Sorcerers Stone</item>
        <item>Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets</item>
        <item>Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban</item>
        <item>Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire</item>
        <item>Harry Potter and the Order of the Pheonix</item>
        <item>Harry Potter and the Half Blood Prince</item>
        <item>Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows</item>
        <item>Harry Potter and the Cursed Child</item>
        <item>The Hobbit</item>
        <item>The Lord of the Rings</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="bookAuthor">
        <item>J.K. Rowling</item>
        <item>J.K. Rowling</item>
        <item>J.K. Rowling</item>
        <item>J.K. Rowling</item>
        <item>J.K. Rowling</item>
        <item>J.K. Rowling</item>
        <item>J.K. Rowling</item>
        <item>J.K. Rowling</item>
        <item>J.R.R Tolkien</item>
        <item>J.R.R Tolkien</item>
    </string-array>

    <integer-array name="bookCover">
        <item>@drawable/harrypotter_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/harrypotter_2</item>
        <item>@drawable/harrypotter_3</item>
        <item>@drawable/harrypotter_4</item>
        <item>@drawable/harrypotter_5</item>
        <item>@drawable/harrypotter_6</item>
        <item>@drawable/harrypotter_7</item>
        <item>@drawable/harrypotter_8</item>
        <item>@drawable/thehobbitbook_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/thelordoftheringsbook_1</item>
    </integer-array>

    <string-array name="bookSynopsys">
        <item>Harry Potter lives with his cruel aunt and uncle, Vernon and Petunia Dursley, and their bullying son, Dudley. On Harrys eleventh birthday, a half-giant named Rubeus Hagrid delivers Harrys acceptance letter to Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry. Harrys parents, James and Lily Potter, were wizards. When Harry was one year old, a dark, evil and powerful wizard who called himself Lord Voldemort killed his parents. Harry survived Voldemorts deadly curse that was thrown at him and is believed to have destroyed the Dark Lord. The curse left a scar in the shape of a lightning bolt on his forehead. Unknown to Harry, he became famous in the wizarding world.</item>
        <item>While spending the summer with the Dursleys, twelve-year-old Harry is visited by a house elf named Dobby. He warned that Harry was in danger and should not return to Hogwarts. Harry refuses, so Dobby magically crashes Aunt Petunia and Uncle Vernons dinner party. An angry Uncle Vernon locks Harry in his room as punishment. The Ministry of Magic immediately sent out a notice accusing Harry of underage magic and threatening to expel him from Hogwarts. Ron Weasley and his twin brothers, Fred and George, arrive at the Dursleys home in their fathers flying Ford Anglia and free Harry, taking him to the Weasleys home. Harry and the rest of the Weasley family visit Diagon Alley to buy school supplies. There, they meet Hermione Granger as well as Lucius Malfoy, the father of Harrys enemy, Draco, and also Gilderoy Lockhart, an arrogant autobiographer and adventurer who is the new Defense Against the Dark Arts teacher at Hogwarts. At Kings Cross station, Harry and Ron cannot get through to Platform 9¾ and miss the Hogwarts Express. They fly in Mr Weasleys car to Hogwarts, crashing into the Whomping Willow in the school yard and breaking Rons wand. The car then fled into the forest.</item>
        <item>Thirteen year old Harry Potter spends his unhappy summer with the Dursleys. After Aunt Marge insults Harry and his late parents, an angry Harry accidentally blows it off. Fearing expulsion from Hogwarts, he ran away. On a dark street, a large black dog watched Harry. Startled, Harry stumbled backwards, causing his wand to emit sparks. The Knight Bus, a magical transport that rescues lost wizards, suddenly appears. Harry leaves for the Leaky Cauldron in Diagon Alley, where Cornelius Fudge, Minister for Magic, is waiting. Harry was not expelled but was asked to remain in Diagon Alley until school started. There, Harry reunited with his best friends Ron Weasley and Hermione Granger. Mr Weasley warns Harry about a wizard named Sirius Black, a convicted murderer who has escaped from Azkaban prison and is believed to be hunting Harry. Dementors, terrifying creatures that guard Azkaban, board the Hogwarts Express train during Harrys journey to school. When one of the Dementors approaches Harry, he relives memories of his parents death, then passes out. The new Defense Against the Dark Arts teacher, Remus Lupine, drives the creature away with a Patronus charm. At Hogwarts, Professor Albus Dumbledore announces that Dementors will be patrolling the school grounds in search of Black.</item>
        <item>In the prologue, which Harry sees through a dream, Frank Bryce, a caretaker of the abandoned Muggle house known as Riddle House, is killed by Lord Voldemort after he catches Voldemort and Wormtail. Harry woke up to his scar hurting. The Weasleys invite Harry and Hermione Granger to watch the Quidditch World Cup, and they travel using a Portkey. After the match, a number of masked Death Eaters, followers of Voldemort, attack the campsite. The Dark Mark shot into the sky, causing mass panic. Harry discovers that his wand is missing, which is later revealed to be held by Winky, Barty Crouchs house elf, which was used to conjure the Dark Mark. Barty Crouch then fired Winky. At Hogwarts, Professor Dumbledore announces that Alastor "Mad-Eye" Moody is the new Defense Against the Dark Arts teacher. Dumbledore also announced that Hogwarts would host the Triwizard Tournament, in which a Hogwarts champion would compete against champions from other wizarding schools. The Goblet of Fire will select a champion from the names entered into it. Only students aged 17 years and over may participate. Because Harry is still underage in the wizarding world, he cannot participate in the Tournament. The Goblet of Fire selected Fleur Delacour from Beauxbatons Academy, Viktor Krum from Durmstrang Institute and Cedric Diggory from Hogwarts. Unexpectedly, the Goblet of Fire chose Harry as the fourth champion, which forced him to compete. Many students, including Ron, believe Harry cheated the Goblet of Fire to get in because he wanted to gain more fame, which causes a fight to break out between Harry and Ron.</item>
        <item>During the summer, Harry Potter and his cousin Dudley Dursley were attacked by dementors. Forced to use magic to expel them, Harry is expelled from Hogwarts, but the decision to expel him is postponed pending a hearing at the Ministry of Magic. A group of wizards who are members of the Order of the Phoenix take Harry to Number 12 Grimmauld Place, Sirius Blacks childhood home. Ron Weasley and Hermione Granger explain that the Order is a secret organization led by Hogwarts headmaster Albus Dumbledore, whose aim is to fight Lord Voldemort and the Death Eaters. Harry, Ron, Hermione, Ginny Weasley and Fred and George Weasley knew that Voldemort was looking for something he did not have before his defeat. The Ministry, led by Cornelius Fudge, refused to accept the fact of Voldemorts return, and ran a smear campaign against Harry and Dumbledore. At his trial, Dumbledore came to Harrys defense and he was cleared of all charges. At Hogwarts, Dolores Umbridge, a senior Ministry employee, is appointed the new Defense Against the Dark Arts teacher. He denies Voldemorts return, and clashes with Harry, causing him to arrest Harry for writing a sentence with a pen that magically engraves "I must not lie" on the back of his hand. When Umbridge refuses to teach the students how to do defensive magic, Harry, Ron, and Hermione form their own Defense club with other students and name it Dumbledores Army. Umbridge, empowered by the Ministry to intervene at Hogwarts as Grand Inquisitor, forbids the formation of all clubs, forcing them to meet and train in secret in the Room of Requirement under Harrys instructions.</item>
        <item>Severus Snape, a member of the Order of the Phoenix, meets Narcissa Malfoy, Dracos mother, and her sister Bellatrix Lestrange, a supporter of Lord Voldemort. Narcissa expresses concern that her son may not be successful in carrying out the mission given to him by Voldemort. Snape made an Unbreakable Vow with Narcissa, vowing to help Draco complete his mission if he failed. Dumbledore picked Harry up at his uncle and aunts house to take him to The Burrow, the home of Harrys best friend, Ron Weasley. They stop at the house of Horace Slughorn, former Potions teacher at Hogwarts. Without realizing it, Harry helped persuade Slughorn to return to teaching. While leaving for Hogwarts on the Hogwarts Express, Harry suspects Draco is a Death Eater. Harry eavesdrops on Draco, who is bragging to his friends about the mission Voldemort assigned him. Draco ambushes Harry, paralyzing and breaking his nose. Nymphadora Tonks finds Harry, fixes his nose and escorts him to Hogwarts. Dumbledore announces that Snape is the new Defense Against the Dark Arts teacher, while Slughorn will teach Potions. Harry finds an old potions textbook, which once belonged to the "Half-Blood Prince", a student who wrote many of the spells and instructions in the book. Harry excels in Potions class, winning a bottle of Felix Felicis or "Lucky Liquid". However, Hermione did not believe the book.</item>
        <item>After Dumbledores death, Voldemort attempted to take control of the Ministry of Magic. Meanwhile, Harry will turn seventeen and will lose the protection of his late mother. Members of the Order of the Phoenix evacuate the Dursleys, and prepare to transport Harry to The Burrow by flying him there, using Harrys friends as bait. Death Eaters attacked them on the way, and in the battle, Mad-Eye Moody and Hedwig were killed while George Weasley was injured. Voldemort comes to kill Harry, but Harrys wand repels Voldemorts attack on its own. Harry, Ron, and Hermione prepare to hunt down Voldemorts four remaining Horcruxes. The three received inheritances from Dumbledore the Golden Snitch for Harry, the Deluminator for Ron, and the fairy tale book "Tales of Beedle the Storyteller" for Hermione. They also inherited the Sword of Godric Gryffindor, which can destroy Horcruxes, but the Ministry does not allow them to keep it. During the wedding of Bill Weasley and Fleur Delacour, the Ministry fell into Voldemorts hands. Death Eaters attack a wedding reception. The third fled to Number 12 Grimmauld Place, Sirius Blacks family home which he had bequeathed to Harry. The Deathly Hallows symbol that appears in the book Tales of Beedle the Storyteller. They learn that Sirius late brother, Regulus, stole the Horcrux locket and hid it in the house. The locket was later stolen by Mundungus Fletcher.</item>
        <item>In the opening scene, set during the epilogue of Deathly Hallows in the year 2017, Harry and Ginny Potter send their younger son, Albus Severus Potter, on the Hogwarts Express to begin his first year at Hogwarts. Harry works as the Head of Magical Law Enforcement at the Ministry of Magic, while Ginny is the editor of the sports section of The Daily Prophet. Ron Weasley and Hermione Granger also send their daughter Rose on the train. Hermione is now the Minister for Magic, while Ron manages Weasleys Wizard Wheezes in Diagon Alley alongside his brother George. Aboard the Hogwarts Express, Albus befriends Scorpius Malfoy, the son of Harrys former foe Draco, and his wife, Astoria. In a break with the tradition of Potters being sorted into Gryffindor, Albus is sorted into Slytherin alongside Scorpius. Both boys are bullied over the next years, with Albus perceived as failing to live up to his parents, and Scorpius being rumoured to be the son of Lord Voldemort. Astoria passes away due to a fatal disease. Albus and Harry drift apart, with Harry being uncertain about how to help Albus. The summer before his fourth year, Albus gets into a fight with Harry, after being given Harrys old baby blanket and a love potion from Ron. During the fight, Harry angrily says that he sometimes wishes Albus was not his son, and Albus spills the potion on the blanket.</item>
        <item>Gandalf tricks Bilbo Baggins into hosting a party for Thorin Oakenshield and his band of twelve dwarves Dwalin, Balin, Kili, Fili, Dori, Nori, Ori, Oin, Gloin, Bifur, Bofur, and Bomburgit , who go over plans reclaiming their ancient home, Lonely Mountain, and its vast treasure from the dragon Smaug. Gandalf unveils Thrors map showing a secret door into the Mountain and proposes that the dumbfounded Bilbo serve as the expeditions "burglar". The dwarves ridicule the idea, but Bilbo, indignant, joins despite himself. The group travels into the wild. Gandalf saves the company from trolls and leads them to Rivendell, where Elrond reveals more secrets from the map. When they attempt to cross the Misty Mountains, they are caught by goblins and driven deep underground. Although Gandalf kills the goblin king and rescues them, Bilbo gets separated from the others as they flee the goblins. Lost in the goblin tunnels, he stumbles across a mysterious ring and then encounters Gollum, who engages him in a game, each posing a riddle until one of them cannot solve it. If Bilbo wins, Gollum will show him the way out of the tunnels, but if he fails, his life will be forfeit. With the help of the ring, which confers invisibility, Bilbo escapes and rejoins the dwarves, improving his reputation with them. The goblins and Wargs give chase, but the company are saved by eagles. They rest in the house of the skin-changer Beorn. </item>
        <item>Bilbo Baggins celebrates his birthday and leaves the Ring to Frodo, his heir. Gandalf a wizard suspects it is a Ring of Power seventeen years later, he confirms it was lost by the Dark Lord Sauron and counsels Frodo to take it away from the Shire. Gandalf leaves, promising to return, but fails to do so. Frodo sets out on foot with his cousin Pippin Took and gardener Sam Gamgee. They are pursued by Black Riders, but meet some Elves, whose singing to Elbereth wards off the Riders. The Hobbits take an evasive shortcut to Bucklebury Ferry, where they meet their friend Merry Brandybuck. Merry and Pippin reveal they know about the Ring and insist on joining Frodo on his journey. They try to shake off the Black Riders by cutting through the Old Forest. Merry and Pippin are trapped by the malign Old Man Willow, but are rescued by Tom Bombadil. Leaving Toms house, they are caught by a barrow-wight. Frodo, awakening from the barrow-wights spell, calls Tom Bombadil, who frees them and gives them ancient swords from the wights hoard. The Hobbits reach the village of Bree, where they meet Strider, a Ranger. The innkeeper gives Frodo an old letter from Gandalf, which identifies Strider as a friend. Knowing the Black Riders will attempt to seize the Ring, Strider guides the group toward the Elvish sanctuary of Rivendell. At Weathertop, they are attacked by five Black Riders. Their leader wounds Frodo with a cursed blade. Strider fights them off and treats Frodo with the herb athelas. They are joined by the Elf Glorfindel, who rides with Frodo, now deathly ill, towards Rivendell. The Black Riders pursue Frodo into the Ford of Bruinen, where they are swept away by flood waters summoned by Elrond.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>